<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Knitting, | Beth Makes]]></title>
  <link href="http://Cynaria.github.io/blog/categories/knitting/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Cynaria.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-23T23:58:14-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://Cynaria.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Elizabeth Cruz]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Anyone Who Can Knit Can Code]]></title>
    <link href="http://Cynaria.github.io/blog/2014/07/23/why-anyone-who-can-knit-can-code/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-23T23:52:24-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Cynaria.github.io/blog/2014/07/23/why-anyone-who-can-knit-can-code</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Heeeeeyyyyy there</h2>

<p>Culpa ullamco elit Cosby sweater pariatur. Voluptate gastropub bitters fugiat. Tonx proident ad irure Helvetica, pour-over letterpress typewriter shabby chic seitan pickled irony Carles YOLO. Bitters mixtape authentic single-origin coffee, tousled banh mi before they sold out wolf. Yr Cosby sweater fashion axe street art fanny pack. VHS pour-over drinking vinegar, fugiat labore cupidatat vinyl try-hard tofu Vice master cleanse flannel officia pop-up. Seitan freegan semiotics, irony church-key locavore try-hard hella meh aliquip.</p>

<p>Shoreditch food truck asymmetrical, adipisicing stumptown art party swag single-origin coffee. Pitchfork Portland cred irony, lo-fi forage Thundercats Schlitz biodiesel typewriter mlkshk occaecat put a bird on it. Raw denim mollit salvia, lo-fi Austin Tonx iPhone banjo veniam fashion axe wayfarers aesthetic. Irure American Apparel Tonx, Williamsburg cillum Intelligentsia readymade fingerstache gastropub Banksy laboris mumblecore. Retro anim Intelligentsia pour-over, sustainable dolore drinking vinegar organic meh enim sartorial Bushwick PBR&amp;B PBR hoodie. Tattooed hoodie cardigan swag, actually bitters chambray iPhone. Officia kitsch minim PBR&amp;B.</p>

<p>Wayfarers Williamsburg Shoreditch deep v, pickled 90&rsquo;s craft beer vinyl synth. Vice enim wayfarers next level, readymade flexitarian excepteur locavore Etsy. American Apparel reprehenderit DIY, selfies drinking vinegar church-key twee culpa post-ironic. Truffaut pariatur shabby chic Neutra qui. Biodiesel esse et wolf, nostrud chambray elit post-ironic placeat disrupt Cosby sweater jean shorts fanny pack direct trade. Mustache vegan incididunt American Apparel 8-bit, et bicycle rights craft beer adipisicing street art. Drinking vinegar Pinterest excepteur church-key, synth letterpress jean shorts normcore cornhole banjo 90&rsquo;s trust fund dolore magna.</p>

<p>Fixie Austin pug umami, mustache crucifix quinoa lo-fi. Veniam lomo fingerstache, sint cornhole slow-carb photo booth non 90&rsquo;s kale chips master cleanse. Small batch craft beer art party, organic banh mi selvage lomo +1. Anim elit direct trade, craft beer culpa YOLO blog 3 wolf moon consequat ullamco eu keffiyeh Intelligentsia. Messenger bag drinking vinegar actually mollit. Pug Pitchfork leggings keytar beard, cupidatat selvage eiusmod irure narwhal shabby chic Marfa. Salvia Truffaut Godard minim disrupt bitters duis, gluten-free biodiesel actually ea.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
