<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Games, | Beth Makes]]></title>
  <link href="http://Cynaria.github.io/blog/categories/games/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Cynaria.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-03T18:34:16-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://Cynaria.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Elizabeth Cruz]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neat Things I Found]]></title>
    <link href="http://Cynaria.github.io/blog/2015/08/03/neat-things-i-found/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-03T15:35:02-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://Cynaria.github.io/blog/2015/08/03/neat-things-i-found</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I found a couple of new things this past week in no particular order. I&rsquo;m sharing! Yaaay for sharing.</p>

<h3><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/camscanner-free-pdf-document/id388627783?mt=8">CamScanner for the iphone</a></h3>

<p>This app is super neat if you want to share pictures you&rsquo;ve drawn but either don&rsquo;t have a decent scanner or you don&rsquo;t have a scanner at all because the one you&rsquo;ve been using for the past&hellip; 13 years has finally bit the dust. It also has an OCR feature that I can&rsquo;t vouch for because it said one of my drawings contains a semi colon.
Before and after!</p>

<p><img class="small" src="/images/posts/2015/08/03/b-mandala.jpg"> <img class="small" src="/images/posts/2015/08/03/a-mandala.jpg"></p>

<!-- more -->


<h3><a href="http://playtheend.com/">The End</a></h3>

<p>This game is super cool. You die immediately (Whoo!) and go to what I would describe as a type of purgatory. It&rsquo;s a platform puzzle game where you can use your light power to create shadows you can walk on! At the end of each level you&rsquo;re given a thought provoking question. Each one draws you closer and closer to a famous figure you&rsquo;re most like. I find it to be a lot of fun but a word of caution: You must be patient! It takes an unfortunate amount of time to load. But I still think it&rsquo;s worth it.</p>

<h3><a href="https://youtu.be/k2YUYPDq7gQ?t=19m32s">Coup</a></h3>

<p>This game is a lot of fun with 3 or more players, but you can play 2 player with some mods. Coup is all about deception or at the very least an ability to figure out when some one&rsquo;s lying or know how to make yourself look like you&rsquo;re lying!</p>

<h3><a href="http://sequel.jeremyevans.net/documentation.html">Sequel</a></h3>

<p>If you&rsquo;re getting tired of the limitations of ActiveRecord then maybe it&rsquo;s high time you tried Sequel. Sequel utilizes a plug-in system. You only take what you need and leave the rest of the junk behind. Because of this, it&rsquo;s far faster to load. <a href="http://twin.github.io/ode-to-sequel/">Learn more about the benefits of Sequel vs ActiveRecord</a>.</p>

<h3>Shrinky Dinks!</h3>

<p>I remember making these when I was a kid. Inspired by a few photos I saw, I searched for a way to make them myself. Queue in some #6 courtesy of Trader Joe&rsquo;s Vegetable egg rolls and a few minutes later I was burning my hands with hot plastic. I&rsquo;m kidding, I&rsquo;m kidding. I might have fingers used to the burn from my ridiculously fast typing&hellip; or because I pick things up with my bare hands when they&rsquo;ve only been out of the oven for a minute, but definitely wait a moment before picking these up. Try this out. It&rsquo;s fun, easy, cheap, and the only limit is how far out of the box you can think. I&rsquo;m planning on making some earrings and stitch markers once I&rsquo;m in possession of a hole punch. But check out the trial runs!</p>

<p><img class="small" src="/images/posts/2015/08/03/shrinky-dinks.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
